dorothyperkins.com 2018-11-29

# Privacy Policy - Dorothy Perkins

**Dorothy Perkins  Privacy Policy - What you need to know**

This is the Dorothy Perkins privacy policy to explain how and why we use your personal information. It’s important, so please read it and make sure you control your privacy. Our website and apps are not intended for use by children who are under 16 years of age. We know you are busy, so to help, our policy lets you chose how much you want to know: quick read, or detail. [+]

**Our privacy principles**

We take your privacy seriously.

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information.

We comply with data privacy laws when using your personal information.

We only use it for lawful reasons you expect or that we explain to you in this document.

We will limit our collection and use to details we really need or which you have provided.

We will explain your rights to control your personal information to you and how to use them.

**Quick read: Privacy Policy Summary**

We want you to understand:

  1. **What personal information we collect about you and where we get it from**
  2. **What we do with your personal information**
  3. **Who we share your personal information with and why**
  4. **Where we send your personal information outside Europe**
  5. **How we keep your personal information secure**
  6. **How long we keep your information and why**
  7. **Your rights and how to use them**
  8. **Other details you should know**

  1. **What personal information we collect about you and where we get it from**

We collect most information directly from you when you order or buy from us. We get technical details from the devices you use to access our apps and websites and from cookies which tell us what you look at online, where and when. Like most other websites, our technology also lets us know when and how you use our websites, such as when you have added to or abandoned your basket or filled in a form.

The personal information we collect and use will depend on why we need it. We will only collect the personal information we believe we need to use, or which you have agreed we can collect from you or agreed someone else can share with us, such as Unidays to confirm student status.

Sometimes we are given information about you unexpectedly, such as from the police, organisations and agencies trying to prevent threats and fraud, and from the public. [In detail][+]

  2. **What we do with your personal information**

We need to collect and use lots of information about you so that you can use our websites and apps, shop in our stores, buy things from us and learn about our offers and new arrivals. We also need to use some details to prevent and detect fraud.

We look at and learn from your browsing, shopping and how you respond to our marketing to understand what sort of customer you are and predict what products we have that you may also be interested in. We try to show you adverts and offers we think you will like tailored to you based on stuff like your location, including what we know about you including through our apps, websites and other websites you visit, relying on the extra understanding about you which ad providers and social media platforms have collected with your consent.

Our use of your details will depend on you and what you are doing: browsing or buying, if you are new to us or a registered customer. Use will be different on-line and in-store but we will try to join up details of our relationship with you in store and online in our records, even if you use different devices online. We explain our lawful reasons for use of your personal information in our detail section. You can access this by scrolling to “Additional Details”.

  3. **Who we share your personal information with and why**

We use suppliers and service providers, such as for delivering orders, or dealing with card checks and payments. These include other group companies and external contractors. We only share the personal details they need to know for their services and we make sure your privacy is respected and protected.

We share personal information with third parties when you have told us that we can share, or them that they can share, or you agree we can share your information, such as when you register to use a ‘Style adviser’ function we offer which is provided by a third party, or with third party ad providers, such as social media platforms or Google, so our adverts are shown to you.  We will share agreed details with third parties like Newday if you choose to use their store card, or Klarna if you choose to use their payment service, for the purpose of enabling the service which you have sought to use.

We will provide personal information about you to the police, fraud prevention and credit reference agencies when we have to by law, or when we deem necessary to prevent fraud.  If we decide to reorganise or sell all or most of our business, your personal information may be transferred to the buyer of the business but we will never sell your personal information to third parties for them to market their products to you.  [In detail][+]

  4. **Where we send your personal information outside Europe**

Business for us and many suppliers is international so your personal information may, at times, be handled in a location outside Europe. When this occurs, we take care in ensuring the security of your information. In the event you ask us to deliver your order outside of Europe, we need to send limited details outside of Europe to fulfil this request. [In detail][+]

  5. **How do we keep your personal information secure**

Our people understand how important it is to keep your personal information safe and secure. We take steps  online and in store  to keep our stores and offices, systems and records secure. [In detail][+]

  6. **How long we keep your information and why**

We will only keep your personal information for a limited period of time. This period will depend on a number of reasons, such whether we still need to deliver to you, or you have an account with us, or we are providing ongoing customer care to you. Sometimes we must also keep your information by law, to deal with a regulator or where required by our insurers. We delete your personal information at your request where possible and we won’t keep it for longer than we should or need to for the provision of a service and for communicating with you. [In detail] [+]

  7. **Your rights and how to use them**

You have rights to find out about how and why we use your personal information and to control its use. These include rights to access and correct your details, in some cases to ask us to limit or stop our use of them and even to delete them.  Where we use your personal information based on your consent, you have the right to change your mind and you can always unsubscribe from our direct marketing to you, by simply clicking unsubscribe in a marketing email, or in this policy.  

Your privacy matters, so we have appointed a Data Protection Officer and have a Data Protection Team to help. You can get in touch with our Customer Care team for help with data protemtion matters at customer.service@dorothyperkins.com. You also have a right to complain to the UK’s privacy regulator should you feel your rights or the law has been compromised.

  8. **Other details you should know.**

Our privacy policy explains how we at Dorothy Perkins are responsible for using your personal information. If you would like to get in touch, you can write to us at: Customer Care, Burton Business Park, Torre Road, Leeds, LS9 7DN, United Kingdom. You can also email us at customer.service@dorothyperkins.com.

From time to time we will update this policy. We’ll always send you a copy in the event of material change but if minor changes are made, we won’t bombard your mailbox. You can, of course, check back here for updates in the mean time! [In detail][+]

**Additional details**

Where we collect and use information about you and which allows us to identify you, it is your personal information. Our quick read summary privacy policy has already given you some key facts but this part of our policy adds further detail if you want to understand more about how and why we use your information.

  1. **What personal information we collect about you and where we get it from**

The personal information we collect and use will depend on why we need it and whether you are buying or browsing, in-store, or online. The technical term for information about you which identifies you is your personal data. We need lots of different types of information and have explained what categories we collect, why it is needed and where we get it from below. Collection and use of this information is not new and is commonly used by lots of retailers, but explaining this level of detail to you is new!

**Category of personal information**

| 

**Examples of your personal information and why we need it**  
  
---|---  
  
Contact information

| 

**What** : Name, Address, Email Address, Telephone Number, account information (user name, log-in details)

**Why** : so we can know who you are to get in touch and for contract, legal and payment reasons as well as administering your account with us

**Where** : from you  
  
Order information

| 

**What** : Contact information, together with purchase details, delivery details, payment details, any communications we have about your order or purchase

**Why** : so we can take your order, take payment for it and make sure it is delivered properly

**Where** : from you  
  
Other delivery information

| 

**What:** Name and address of recipient for delivery, if different from customers

**Why:** so we can deliver to the person at the address which you have requested

**Where** : from you  
  
Payment / card information

| 

**What** : Name, card issuer and card type, number, issue number, start and expiry dates and cvv code; gift/store card details if used; Klarna account details if used

**Why** : so we can check the right person is using the right card/account and meet the payment requirements of the card/account issuers; and make sure we are paid for what you buy

**Where** : from you, your payment /card issuer, your store card provider if used, or Klarna if chosen by you  
  
Legal information

| 

**What** : Fraud checks or flags raised about your transactions, the payment card you want to use, payment card refusals, suspected crimes, complaints, claims and accidents

**Why** : so we can protect you, other customers and our business against criminal activities and risks, make sure we understand and can meet our legal obligations to you and others and can defend ourselves

**Where** : from you, the police, crime and fraud prevention agencies, payment card providers, the public, regulators, your and our professional advisors and representatives  
  
Preference information

| 

**What** : Your marketing preferences, your account settings including any default preferences, any preferences you have indicated, such as country, language and currency, the types of products/offers that interest you, or the areas of our website that you visit

**Why** : so we can make your visits easier and more convenient and make sure you get the information you want from us in the way we think you  will like

**Where** : from you, from our website/app technology interaction with your browser/devices and cookies tracking the pages you visit, the marketing messages you open and the links you follow  
  
Communications

| 

**What** : Communications we may have with you, whether relating to an order or not. Please note that we record calls to our customer care centre team. Details of your reviews and how you rate us

**Why** : so we can deal with your requests, help you, meet your needs and make sure we have accurate records. It also helps us to obtain customer feedback and improve as a result.

**Where** : from you and occasionally from any third parties involved, such as another visitor to our store  
  
Voluntary information

| 

**What** : Any voluntary information you provide us with, such as your date of birth, favourite & worst colour/style, responses to surveys or competition entries; student discount details and social media account details

**Why** : so we can get to know you better; make our communications with you more personal; get in touch on your birthday; make sure we are not marketing/selling to children; learn and improve from your survey feedback, organise in store events and pick competition winners

**Where** : from you, your social media account provider and student body, such as Unidays  
  
Observed information

| 

**What** : CCTV images of you in and around entrances and exits to our stores and offices. Your customer journey around our store from Wi-Fi connectivity or comparable technology use

**Why** : so we can keep you, other customers, our staff, buildings, systems and data safe and secure; provide you with Wi-Fi in our stores and so we can better understand how customers want to shop in our stores, popular routes and areas and where we should place different products and what to market to you

**Where** : from you; from our CCTV and from our W-Fi and similar technology interaction with your devices

**What** : Your customer journey on line and how you use our websites and apps and use your devices when doing so. Whether and when you open our marketing emails and respond to our adverts. When you are on our website, our website technology is able to collect the technical details of your mouse clicks and movements, page scrolling and text content you key in to our online forms but will not collect payment card numbers or name and address type details

**Why** : so we can understand how many customers use our websites and apps, what works best online and in our marketing and advertising and what we need to change and improve to attract and keep your attention

**Where** : from you; from our website/app technology interaction with your browser/devices and cookies tracking the pages you visit  
  
Device information

| 

**What** : IP address, internet provider, operating system and browser used, type of device, such as laptop or smart phone, device cookie settings and other device details, such as MAC address and the geographic region which your device reports to us that you are located in

**Why** : so our website and app technology can work properly with your device and make sure you can see and use our intended website and apps on the device you are using

**Where** : from you; from our website/app technology interaction with your browser/devices  
  
Marketing information

| 

**What** : Your customer journey before and after visiting our store from Google beacons. Details of your online browsing activities on our website, such as the pages, products or areas of our website that you visit, or which link has brought you to our website from our email communication. Without getting or knowing the details they collect, benefitting from similar information about your use of other websites which is available to ad providers, social media platforms and Google, who help us to show you on other websites our ads tailored to the category of customer they think you are and which we are targeting. Similar details from use of our apps. Your contact information, historic order information, preference information, voluntary information and online observed information

**Why** : so we can learn more about you; try to understand the type of customer you are, to predict what you are most interested in, what offers you will like most, tailor our adverts and offers

**Where** : from you, from our website/app technology interaction with your browser/devices and cookies tracking the pages you visit; without seeing the details collected, from cookies set by ad providers, social media platforms and Google  
  
There are also “special categories” of more sensitive personal information which require a higher level of protection, such as information about a person’s health, criminal offences, sexuality, race, ethnicity, health or disability.  
  
Accident information

| 

**What** : details about any accident or injury on our premises, or health incident

**Why** : so we can get you the help you need, deal with the emergency services, insurance and claims

**Where** : from you, witnesses or observed about you  
  
Suspected crime information

| 

**What** : details of your identity, image, name and address, suspected or alleged thefts, fraud, assault or other criminal behaviour

**Why** : so we can protect customers, the public and our business against risks and crime

**Where** : from crime and fraud prevention agencies , from you, witnesses, and from the police  
  
**Concessions**

Where you shop in one of our concessions in another retailer’s store, their systems will check and take and record payment, operate CCTV and security and Wi-Fi. They will provide us with details of your purchases for our records. Unusually, if you are involved in any suspected incident, they may share additional details with us to help us together to prevent and detect crime.

**Cookies**

So we are clear, cookies are the nickname for tiny text files which some websites pages place on the device you use to access them, to give us encrypted information such as to remember what you have put in your basket when shopping, your preferences, whether you have an account and what cookies you have accepted. They will not collect your name, address and payment card details but send back technical facts.  They also help us to understand and sort out technical errors which sometimes happen online. We need cookies to make our websites and your device able to work well together. Some cookies are our own but we also work with carefully selected third parties to help us and who set their cookies from our website pages and to help us run our websites (these are called third party cookies).  You will not be able to buy from us online and your browsing experience may not be as enjoyable if you block your device from receiving cookies.

We use cookies online to do the job a good sales assistant does in store, noting what you are interested in, seeing if we can help show you where those items are, find more like them and tell you about products which work well with them. We can also tell you about special offers and promotions, just like they would.

Personal information does not include information where your identity has been removed or is unknown (anonymous data).  Some of this information may only be identifiable to you and personal because you are logged in to your account, or because we have collected details of your IP address or the device that you have used to access the website. Where we can, we prefer to show you adverts online which you are more likely to be interested in.

Normally until you buy from us, you are an unnamed user of our website but we want to make you a customer. We work with online advertising partners to do this. They set a cookie from our webpages and this allows them to spot when you use the same device on other websites they publish ads on. They can then make sure you see an ad from us (retargeting). In some cases, the ads you see from us online will be more tailored to you (tailored or behavioural ads). This uses known and observed information about you to try and categorise you and predict what you will want to buy and which offers you will most like (profiling). This will be from our knowledge of you as a customer with us and from your use of our websites but we do not share that detailed information with those advertising partners. In other cases, it will be based on what advertising partners /social media providers know about you from their cookies and use of their websites but we do not receive the detailed information from these websites. 

You can get more information about cookies and can change your mind about cookies at any time. if you want more details or to change your mind, see our cookies notice.

  2. **What we do with your personal information**

We need to collect and use lots of information about you and any devices you use to access our apps or websites for many different reasons but we will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. This will always be for one of these reasons (our lawful basis):

**Legal basis**

| 

**When we use this basis**  
  
---|---  
  
Contract

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information for a contract reason (to comply with a contract with you, or take steps you have requested to start a contract with you).  
  
Legal obligation

| 

This is where we must use your personal information to comply with the law, or a binding request like a court order.  
  
Consent

| 

This is where we use your personal information with your clear consent, you have a complete free choice to say yes or no, and you can change your mind at any time.  
  
Public interest

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information for an official purpose, or for a reason in the public interest for the greater public good, like cooperating voluntarily with an official police investigation.  
  
Vital interests

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information in an emergency to protect you (or someone else) from death or serious harm.  
  
Legitimate interests

| 

This is where, on balance and being fair to you, we have (or a third party has) another good and lawful business reason for using your personal information and we do not need your consent.  
  
By law we must treat special category or sensitive personal data, such as on health or alleged crimes, with even more care and must have an additional reason for collecting and using this type of personal information. Where special categories of sensitive personal information are involved in addition our use will always be for one of these reasons.

**Legal basis**

| 

**When we use this basis**  
  
---|---  
  
Legal obligation

| 

This is where we must use your personal information to comply with your or our legal rights or obligations related to employment or social protection.  
  
Preventative medicine

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information for medical diagnosis or preventative health reasons  
  
Substantial public interest

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information in the substantial public interest for the greater public good.  
  
Explicit consent

| 

This is where we use your personal information with your very clear and express consent, you have a complete free choice to say yes or no, and you can change your mind at any time.  
  
Legal claims

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information to investigate, take advice on bring or defend legal claims.  
  
Vital interests

| 

This is where we need to use your personal information in an emergency to protect you (or someone else) from death or serious harm and you are not capable of giving your consent.  
  
We want you to understand why we use the personal information we do and our legal basis for doing so. We explain this here.

Where we can, we will also move from using your information in ‘individual picture’ form about you, to ‘big picture’ form as a member of a group but not as an individual. To do this, we can bunch lots of information on individuals together (aggregation), remove or change details that identify you to make that more difficult or impossible (de-identification, pseudonymisation and anonymization) and change information about people into information about numbers (statistics). This helps us to protect your privacy whilst having the information we need to run our business and comply with our obligations. We can use the details for research, statistical analysis, and reports.

**Why we use your personal information**

| 

**Lawful basis for use**  
  
---|---  
  
**All personal information**

| 

**Sensitive personal information**  
  
To check stock for you, put it on hold, arrange to send it to your local store and keep you updated on this

| 

Contract

|   
  
To accept your orders, check and take payment, deliver your order and communicate with you about it. This may include a gift delivered to another person or delivery to another address if you want

Dealing with returns, replacements and refunds we are obliged to deal with

You may want to use any optional delivery tracking or confirmation facility or update options we offer. This mean sharing additional contact information for you with our delivery partners and you using their delivery systems

Dealing with returns, replacements and refunds we are not obliged to deal with

| 

Contract

Contract; Legal obligation

Legitimate interests

Legitimate interests

|   
  
To accept card payments, we need to comply with anti-money laundering legal obligations and comply with the rules of the card issuers eg Visa to make sure we get paid

This means checking your identity and that your use of the card appears lawful by checking with credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies who may keep records of this and of any concerns.  We use specialist payment providers to help with this.

Preventing and detecting crime is important to everyone and any concerns may be shared with law enforcement agencies

| 

Legitimate interests; Legal obligation

| 

Substantial public interest; Legal claims  
  
To ask you about student discount registration, fill in surveys, provide feedback and deal with your queries and requests

To learn from your feedback and improve

| 

Legitimate interests

|   
  
To deal with your queries, requests and respond to any customer care concerns.

To provide you with information about your order or request we think you need.

Sometimes this will be where this involves a legal right or obligation we must comply with and unusually this may relate to legal claims

| 

Legitimate interests; Legal obligation

| 

Legal claims  
  
To provide you with Wi-Fi in our stores to make you more likely to visit and stay shopping with us

| 

Legitimate interests

|   
  
To respond to your personal shopping requests, book appointments and provide personal shopping services

| 

Contract

|   
  
To set up your account with us and run it to make your online shopping experience quicker and easier for you, including dealing with related requests and changes and communications

Storing any payment card details with your consent

| 

Legitimate interests; Explicit consent

|   
  
Managing any accidents, injuries or health incidents which occur in store.

Meeting our health and safety legal obligations.

Dealing with any related insurance or legal claims

| 

Legitiamte interests; Legal obligation; Vital interests

| 

Vital interests; Preventative medicine; Legal obligation; Legal claims; Substantial public interest  
  
Managing any suspected fraud, shoplifting or other suspected criminal activity involving or affecting you

Responding to warnings and providing details to law enforcement and fraud prevention agencies to investigate, prevent and detect crime.

Dealing with any related insurance or legal claims

| 

Legal obligation; Legitimate interests

| 

Legal claims; Substantial public interest

Legal obligation  
  
To keep evidence of our dealings with you to comply with our legal obligations, including on accounting, taxation and data privacy

To keep records for risk management and insurance purposes

| 

Legal obligation

Legitimate interests

|   
  
Grouping individual records together in large numbers to analyse them to understand customer group interests, trends and changes across the customer base.

This needed to run our business  efficiently, including ordering stock and organising supplies and adjusting resourcing such as for in store staff / delivery coverage to meet demand

| 

Legitimate interests

|   
  
To keep our systems, websites and their use under continual review to check and maintain their integrity and security and proper operation and continually improve their efficiency

Meeting our obligations to secure personal information

| 

Legitimate interests; Legal obligation

|   
  
To authenticate users, account holders and ensure use of our website complies with our terms and policies

| 

Legitimate interests; Legal obligation

|   
  
To deal with our legal obligations, such as on product recalls, and binding requests for information, such as from courts

| 

Legal obligation

| 

Legal claims  
  
To cooperate with and disclose information to law enforcement and official agencies and government, regulators  courts and other parties even where not legally binding.

This is where we believe it is needed to prevent or detect crime, or help with legal compliance or good governance

This includes where we take professional advice to understand and deal with our legal rights and obligations and dealing with our insurers

| 

Legitimate interests; Public interest

| 

Substantial public interest

Legal claims  
  
To deal with the reorganisation or sale if our business or part of it and sharing details needed with buyers and their professional advisers

| 

Legitimate interests

|   
  
**Marketing based on our legitimate interests is to try to ...**  
  
---  
  
Legitimate interests

| 

  * learn more about you from your browsing and purchase history, how you like to shop and how you respond to our ads and offers, we do this to try and anticipate what demographic, age range, region and preferences you would like

o    try and categorise you, predict more accurately what you will want to buy, what offers and ads you will prefer and provide you with those tailored offers and ads we think you will like most

  * so we can -

o    generate new customers and convert possible customers into actual customers

o    convert browsers to shoppers

o    encourage current customers to buy more goods from us or buy more frequently

o    encourage customers also to buy in store if they only buy online, or to also buy online if they only buy in store

o    generate income and profit to run our business

o    fund our development of new exciting products for you

o    pay to attract, retain and expand our amazing and talented staff who we need to do this  
  
**Marketing based on consent…**  
  
---  
  
Consent

| 

  * To provide you with the app you have requested and send you push notifications with ads, special offers, promotions and news
  * To email you with ads, special offers, news and promotions
  * To ask you to provide product reviews and to rate us
  * To use your location to send you location related advertising
  * To host and run events, including invitation only events, student nights and fashion shows, with your consent if you sign up rather than simply turn up
  * To host and run events, including invitation only events, student nights and fashion shows, with your consent if you sign up rather than simply turn up
  * By signing you up to our email marketing to promote products
  * If you are logged in to your account  with us with your mobile device / have one of our apps and your device connects to our Wi-Fi in store, tracking your journey through our store by linking your journey and your account
  * To link your social media account(s) with your activities on our websites and then showing you targeted product recommendations
  * Sharing details of your purchases from us with third party style adviser providers where you have registered an account for this and agreed to such sharing

Where we carry out marketing this will be based on our legitimate interests unless by law we need your consent or have chosen to ask for consent anyway. In the event you have placed an order, query, request or flagged an issue, we will still need to keep in touch. We won’t market to you but contact you regarding the relevant issue.  

Where we have explained that our use of your personal information is needed for us to comply with a legal obligation, or to start or comply with a contract with you, if you refuse to provide those details, on most occasions, we won’t be able to accept your order or continue to deal with your purchase or delivery.

  3. **Who we share your personal information with and why**

We do not sell your personal information to third parties for them to market their products to you but, on occasion, we do need to share some of your details with third parties.

We need to work with other group companies, suppliers and professional service providers as they help us to run our business and look after you. In these cases, we only share the personal details they need to know for their services and work closely with them to make sure your privacy is respected and protected. They must keep your details confidential and secure and only use them to provide the help we have agreed with them or as allowed by law.

We are a dynamic business in a fast moving industry and as you can imagine, the help we need can change quickly and over time. We work with lots of suppliers and service providers and these also frequently change. So that you understand where this can affect your personal information, we have provided more details.

**Who we share your personal information with and why**  
  
---  
  
Who we share with

| 

Why we share it  
  
Group companies

| 

We are part of the Arcadia group of companies and different companies within the group help with different functions. For instance:

  * the operation of our websites and apps;
  * digital and marketing;
  * customer care;
  * data protection support, legal, risk, compliance and insurance.
  * As normal for companies, we also need to report up to our parent company and it will be involved with key decision making related to our business. 

Where we have two or more of our brands sharing a single store, and you buy products from one brand but pay at another brand’s checkout, the brand who you buy from will share details about your in store purchase with the brand whose products you buy  
  
External suppliers

| 

We use external suppliers to help us with:

  * warehouses, packing and delivering orders;
  * payment service providers to securely vaslidate and take your payments by card;
  * specialist providers to host and operate our websites, online presence, databases and IT systems and support their operation and help with data analytics;
  * specialist providers to help with cyber and other security; and
  *  agencies to help with marketing, analytics, advertising and communications.

Store cards and credit providers

| 

We will need to share agreed personal information about your purchases with third parties providers, such as:

  * Newday if you choose to use their store card; or
  * Klarna if you choose to use their payment service.

Their privacy policies apply to their use of your details.  
  
Event, discount registration and account providers

| 

We can share personal information with third parties for discount verification, registered account management, event management  or where you have told us, or them, we can share it. This includes:

  * Unidays for student registration; and
  * When you register to use any ‘Style adviser’ functions we offer which are provided by a third party

Other retailers

| 

Where we operate a concession in another retailer’s store, their systems record your personal information. Unusually, there may be an incident involving you where we need to provide them with details about you to prevent and detect crime or help them to deal with legal claims or obligations  
  
Cookies*

| 

We explained above how we use cookies with third parties.

  * Where you accept third party cookies, we do not send them data but they normally collect data directly from your device

Social media*

| 

  * Where you want to link your social media account to us, we will share the details needed to do that with your provider.  

Third party content and links on our websites*

| 

  * Our websites and apps sometimes feature links to third parties which we think you will like
  * We do not send them your details but if you follow those links, you will do so direct and leave our website. You can choose to share your personal data with them separately sand subject to their Privacy Notice

Law enforcement, credit reference and fraud prevention agencies

| 

We will provide personal information about you to:

  * the police;
  * fraud prevention and credit reference agencies

if we must by law, or when we think it is necessary to prevent fraud, or protect you, our staff, business or other customers, from threats, theft or, fraud  
  
Business buyers

| 

If we decide to reorganise or sell all or most of our business:

  * to the buyer of the business, their professional advisers and related partners who need to know

Other recipients

| 

We may also disclose your personal information where needed to comply with a legal obligation, to enforce a contract or to protect the rights, property or safety of you, our employees, customers or others, or where permitted by law and needed to help others to do so.

  * Consultants and professional advisors including legal advisors, accountants and auditors;
  * courts, court-appointed persons/entities, receivers and liquidators;
  * business partners and joint ventures;
  * insurers; and
  * governmental departments, statutory and regulatory bodies including the Information Commissioner’s Office, the police and Her Majesty’s Revenue and Customs.

*The way the internet works means that to show you our banners and adverts especially on other websites and apps, we must work with third party ad exchanges, networks and online platforms. They must comply with their data privacy obligations, make their policies available to you and allow you to change your mind about their cookies and use of your information. We are not responsible for their use of your personal information or websites.

  4. **Where we send your personal information outside Europe**

Data privacy laws in the UK and across the countries in the European Union, Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein, (the European Economic Area) are very similar.  We have called this area ‘Europe’ for ease. If it is necessary for us to transfer your personal information outside Europe we will only make that transfer if we use a method approved as privacy-safe by the data privacy regulators in Europe:, including:

  * the country to which the personal information is to be transferred has been approved by them; 
  * the recipient of the personal information is in the USA and has certified they will comply with the Privacy Shield rules to protect personal information, approved by them;
  * the recipient of the personal information is legally bound to protect your personal information under binding corporate rules approved by them;
  * we have made sure that there is a contract to protect your personal data with the recipient, using a template approved by them;
  * the transfer is needed for another reason approved by them, such as to make an international delivery at your request; or
  * where you explicitly consent to the transfer

You can ask for a copy of the method approved as privacy safe by the data privacy regulators in Europe from our Customer Care team or Data Protection Team using the contact details in section 8 below.

  5. **How do we keep your personal information secure**

We take specific steps required by data privacy law to take appropriate care of your personal information, whether online or not. This is to protect it against theft or other loss, being corrupted so we cannot use it properly or at all and to stop people who should not be able to see or use it from doing so.  

  6. **How long we keep your information and why**

We will only keep your personal information for a limited period of time. This will depend on a number of factors, including:

  * whether you have placed an order with us, or have a registered account with us;
  * any laws or regulations that we are required to follow;
  * whether we are dealing with a current request, customer care issue or complaint;
  * where there is a legal or other type of dispute involving or affecting you;
  * the type of information that we hold about you; and
  * whether we are asked by you or a regulatory authority to keep your personal data for a valid reason.

We will keep your personal information during the period that you are a customer with us and then for as long as is necessary in connection with both our and your legal rights and obligations. This may mean that we keep some types of personal information for longer than others. Generally, if you are an inactive customer we will remove your account after 18 months.

  7. **Your rights and how to use them**

You have rights to understand and control use of your personal information. These rights only apply to your own personal information. For all these rights:

  * we must be able to verify your identity;
  * your request must not impact the privacy rights of other people;
  * Your request must not be excessive, very unreasonable or repeated [too often].
  * They cannot clash with the provision of a service (for example submitting a right to erasure when we are processing an order from you)

Many rights have limitations and exceptions, for instance, we do not have to provide you with legally privileged advice involving your personal information.

**Your right**

| 

**What does it mean?**

| 

**Limitations and conditions of your right**  
  
---|---|---  
  
**Right of access**

| 

You are entitled to have access to your personal information and specific information about its use by us (this is more commonly known as submitting a “data subject access request”).

| 

You should specify the type of information you would like to see to ensure that our disclosure is meeting your expectations.  
  
**Rights in relation to inaccurate personal or incomplete data**

| 

You may challenge the accuracy or completeness of your personal information and have it corrected or add details to make it complete.

You must inform us of changes to your personal information. Please notify us of any changes as soon as they occur, including changes to your contact details.

| 

Where available, please use any self-help tools to correct the personal information we use about you.

When exercising this right, please be as specific as possible.  
  
**Right to object to our use of your personal information**

| 

**You have the right to object** to our use of your personal information.

| 

This general right applies where our use of your personal information is needed based on legitimate interests and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground.

We will then consider your request.  
  
**Right to object to direct marketing**

| 

You can change your mind about direct marketing at any time. This may mean changing your mind about our app, or receiving our emails, or all direct marketing.

| 

Click unsubscribe at the bottom of any email.  
  
**Right to object to important computer only decision making affecting you**

| 

If we have explained that we use any computer only decision making to make important decisions affecting you, you have the right to challenge those decisions and have a real person take another look at them to make sure they were right.

| 

The second look at the decision by a real person may result in the same decision the computer made.  
  
**Right to restrict our use of your personal information**

| 

You are entitled to limit our use of your personal information for so long as we are considering any request you have made for us to  correct or complete your personal information, or to consider an objection you have made to our use of it based on legitimate interests.

You can also request us to limit our use permanently in some cases.

| 

The temporary restriction on our use will end when we have dealt with your request for correction or completion of your personal information or we have made a decision on further use following your objection.

If we agree that we should stop that use of your personal information, or in limited other cases, the limitation will become permanent.

The impact of the restriction is limited to personal information affected by the request/use.  
  
**Right to erasure**

| 

You are entitled to have your personal information deleted or destroyed, such as where your personal information is no longer needed for its intended use.

| 

We may not always be able to erase your personal information completely, such as were we still need it to comply with a legal obligation, or to deal with legal claims.  
  
**Right to withdrawal of consent**

| 

Where our processing of your personal information is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time.

| 

If you withdraw your consent, this will only affect future use of that personal information.  
  
**Right to data portability**

| 

You are entitled to receive the personal information which you have provided to us and which is used by us in a commonly used format to help make it readily re-usable.

| 

This right only applies where we are using the personal information you have provided based on your consent or on our contract with you.  
  
To unsubscribe, or change your mind about receiving our marketing, you can:

  * use the unsubscribe link in our emails
  * email our Customer Care team customer.service@dorothyperkins.com
  * call our Customer Care team
  * write to us at the above listed address

We are committed to protecting your privacy, so we have appointed a Data Protection Officer and have a Data Protection Team to help. If you wish to exercise any of these rights please contact our Customer Care team by emailing customer.service@dorothyperkins.com

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the UK data privacy regulator.

  8. **Other details you should know.**

Our privacy policy explains how we at **Dorothy Perkins** use your personal information. If you would like to get in touch, you can write to us.

**Dorothy Perkins Limited GDPR Cookies Policy**

Our website uses cookies to collect information.

1.What is a cookie?  
2.Use of cookies on this website  
3.Why we use cookies  
4.Our cookies  
    4.1.Strictly functional cookies  
    4.2.Statistical cookies  
    4.3.Personalisation cookies  
    4.4.Marketing cookies

    4.5 Cookies used in mobile apps  
5.Third party cookies  
    5.1.What third party cookies do we use and why  
    5.2.Flash cookies  
    5.3.Social buttons  
6.How to manage cookies  
7.Checking which browser you use  
    7.1.PCs  
    7.2.MAC  
8.Other details you should know

**1.What is a cookie?**  
Cookies are small files of letters and numbers that are downloaded onto your computer or mobile or other handheld device when you access certain websites. Cookies allow a website to recognise a user’s device and help your browser navigate through the website by allowing you to log in automatically or remembering settings you selected during earlier visits (among other functions). Cookies do not harm your computer. If you would like to learn more about cookies in general you can visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

**2.Use of cookies on this website**  
Cookies help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse this website and allow you to make full use of the online shopping and personalised features available on this website. We do not use cookies to collect or record information such as your name, address or payment details. Sometimes we link information from cookies with you, such as when you are using our website and logged in to your account. In such cases the combined data is your personal information and you should also read our [privacy policy](http://www.dorothyperkins.com/PRIVACY-POLICY).

**3.Why we use cookies**  
We use cookies on this website for the following main purposes:

  * **Strictly Functional Cookies** : for technical purposes essential for the operation of this website and / or your use of it, such as keeping track of your current shopping session and enabling you to proceed to checkout and pay for products;
  * **Measurement and Analytics Cookies** : to collect statistical information about how visitors use this website, calculate views, analyse popular products by quantifying clicks. This is so we can improve the way this website works and measure the success of competitions and campaigns;
  * **Personalisation Cookies:** to distinguish you from other users of this website, so we can personalise your shopping experience and allow us to improve your use of the website. These help ensure all that is displayed on our site is more relevant to your interests and so we can remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the country you are in)
  * **Marketing Cookies:** to ensure the marketing content that you receive on sites other than our own is relevant and reflects the interests you have shown when browsing on our site.
  * **Third party cookies** : used by third parties to collect data when you are on our website and sometimes when you are on other websites. We do not receive their data. They can be used for any of the above reasons but are mainly used to help provide behavioural targeted advertising to you online. These also enable us to fulfil our contractual obligations to third parties, for example to pay a partner if you have made a purchase on this website by following a link from their website.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies when they are dropped on your computer, mobile or other handheld device. You can adjust your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies. By accepting cookies when visiting our website, you consent to cookies being used in accordance with this Cookies Policy. You can change your mind at any time about your consent. If you do not consent to cookies, or have changed your mind about cookies, you must either disable cookies through your browser or refrain from using this website. Please go to'How To Manage Cookies' section below for information on how to manage and disable cookies.

4.Our cookies

**4.1 Strictly functional cookies**  
These cookies help make a website useable and are essential in helping you move around our site and use it’s features. Without these cookies you would not be able navigate our site and gain access to secure areas such as signing into your account, add something to the basket or make purchases.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Apache

| 

Apache

| 

This helps the website run cookies, without this the website would not work  
  
akacd_monty-prod, Pakaas_DRET  
akaas_Checkout_AB, akavpau_VP_DP

| 

Arcadia Akamai (Internal)

| 

Used to identify which Monty site/AB test you are running on  
  
dual-run, traceId2, PHPSESSID, source, cookietest, se_t - Active Queue, se_q - Active Queue, se - Queue Processing, se – Queue, se - Error Count, se - Active Queue, tempsession

| 

Arcadia (Internal)

| 

These cookies are used to support the website and user experience, without these the website would not work  
  
userPreferredUrl, userLanguage, usergeo, userCountry, prefShipCtry

| 

Arcadia WCS (Internal)

| 

These cookies remember your preferences from previous visits, allow you to add to basket and store your shopping basket. The website wouldn't work for you without them  
  
wcsstore/ConsumerDirectStorefrontAssetStore/images/trans_pixel.gif, WC_USERACTIVITY_-1002, WC_SESSION_ESTABLISHED, WC_PERSISTENT, WC_GENERIC_ACTIVITYDATA, WC_AUTHENTICATION_-1002, WC_ACTIVEPOINTER, jsessionid, WC_AUTHENTICATION_#, WC_USERACTIVITY_#

| 

IBM

| 

These cookies remember your preferences from previous visits, allow you to add to basket and store your shopping basket. The website wouldn't work for you without them  
  
test_cookie

| 

doubleclick (Google)

| 

Used to check if the user's browser supports cookies  
  
AWSELB

| 

Amazon Web Services

| 

Used to distribute traffic to the website on several servers in order to optimise response times  
  
JSESSIONID

| 

nr-data.net

| 

Preserves users states across page requests  
  
**4.2 Statistical cookies**  
These cookies help us to understand how users interact with our site and provide statistical analysis of our site. In order to keep our site easy to use, working properly and up-to-date, we use web analytics services to help us understand how people use our site. For example we see which areas are most popular, identify when errors occur and can test different features to see which works best.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
s_vnum, s_vi, s_sq, s_ppvl, s_ppv, s_ppn, s_nr, s_lv_s, s_lv, s_invisit, s_fid, s_cc

| 

Adobe

| 

 These cookies enable SiteCatalyst analytics software, supplied by Adobe. This software helps us take and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity and shopping times. That information helps us to improve the website and your shopping experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant.  
  
mostRecentProp19

| 

Arcadia (Internal)

| 

These cookies are used to support the website and user experience, without these the website would not work  
  
en-persist

| 

ecustomeropinions.com

| 

Collects customer feedback data. Used by Mopinion  
  
_utmz, _utmt, _utmc, _utmb, _utma, _utm.gif, _gid, _gali, _ga

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Collects data on where the user came from, what search engine was used , what link was clicked and what search term was used . Used by Google Analytics  
  
GTM-Store, _dc_gtm_UA-#

| 

Google Tag Manager

| 

These cookies map your visit to the website. We get an overall picture of how our visitors shop in our website. This information allows us to provide the best possible shopping experience.  
  
Pastease.passive.activated.333Zm7lTPEczxtL, Pastease.passive.chance.333Zm7lTPEczxtL

| 

Mopinion

| 

Register whether embedded form has been activated  
  
**4.3 Personalization cookies**  
These cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves and looks. These allow us to remember the choices you make (such as language and region you are in).

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
PugT, PUBMDCID

| 

pubmatic.com

| 

Registers a unique ID that identifies the user's device during return visits across websites that use the same ad network . The ID is used to allow targeted ads  
  
_mibhv

| 

Moveable Ink

| 

This cookie is used for general purpose behaviour tracking, outside of the context of any specific campaign  
  
**4.4 Marketing cookies**  
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual. Without these cookies online adverts you encounter will be less relevant to you and your interests.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
CMDD, CMID, CMPRO, CMPS, CMRUM3, CMSC, CMST

| 

Casalemedia

| 

to make advertising more engaging and relevant to users and more valuable to publishers and advertiser  
  
xyz_cr_100136_et_100

| 

Cheetahmail

| 

To help offer relevent marketing emails to the customer  
  
IDE

| 

doubleclick (Google)

| 

Real time bidding advertising exchange  
  
fr

| 

facebook.com

| 

Used by Facebook to deliver a series of advertisement products such as real time bidding from third party advertisers  
  
collect

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Used to send data to Google Analytics about the visitor's device and behaviour. Tracks the visitor across devices and marketing channels  
  
ads/user-lists/#, ads/ga-audiences

| 

google.com

| 

Contains a unique ID that Google uses to remember your preferences and other information, such as your preferred language (e.g. English), how many search results you wish to have shown per page (e.g. 10 or 20) and whether or not you wish to have Google’s SafeSearch filter turned on. These are also used to create remarketing based on user behavior on the site  
  
i

| 

openx.net

| 

Registers technical user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network  
  
peerius_user, peerius_sess, peerius_rid, peerius_ct 

| 

Peerius

| 

These cookies enable Peerius software. This software allows us to make recommendations of products that we think might be of interest to you, based on what you and other visitors have viewed  
  
PugT, PUBMDCID, KRTBCOOKIE_#

| 

pubmatic.com

| 

Registers a unique ID that identifies the user's device during return visits across websites that use the same ad network . The ID is used to allow targeted ads  
  
Queue That - Queue Processing, Queue That – Queue, Queue That - Error Count, Queue That - Active Queue, qubit_platform, qb_UserType, qb_session, qb_persist_test, qb_permanent, _qubitVistory, _qubitVisitorId, _qubitUACategorisation, _qubitTracker_s, _qubitTracker, _qubitTabID, _qubitPingQueueLock, _qubitPingQueue, _qubitFlips, _qst_s, _qst, _qsst_s, _qsst, x_qtag_48652, _qPageNum_dorothyperkins_uk_mobile, x_qtag_montydorothyperkinsukmobile, _qPageNum_dpeu_mobile, qbef, qbeft, _qPageNum_dpeu

| 

Qubit

| 

 These cookies enable Qubit analytics software. This software helps us take and analyse visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, response to marketing activity and shopping times. That information helps us to improve the website and your shopping experience, and to make our marketing campaigns relevant. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.  
  
tap.php, rpx, rpb, put_#, khaos, c

| 

rubiconproject.com

| 

Registers technical user data, such as IP address, geographical location, visited websites, and what ads the user has clicked, with the purpose of optimising ad display based on the user's movement on websites that use the same ad network  
  
smc_sesn, smc_spv, smc_tpv, smc_uid, smc_v4_7922, smc-dv2, smc-loc-3080917982-, smct_last_ov, smct_session, smc-loc-946721084-, 1074-1-1-0-0-24-6-47995-7922/px2.png

| 

smct

| 

Used for serving promotional advert  
  
id

| 

yieldlab.net

| 

Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user's device. The ID is used for targeted ads  
  
tuuid, um, umeh, tuuid_last_update

| 

360 Yield

| 

Measuring the conversion. This aggregate information is used to determine the value of and to settle with an advertising partner  
  
**4.5 C** **ookies used in mobile Apps**

These cookies are used in our Mobile Apps. They are strictly functional and help make the app useable and are essential in helping you move around our site and use it’s features. Without these cookies you would not be able navigate our site and gain access to secure areas such as signing into your account, add something to the basket or make purchases.

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Provider**

| 

**Purpose**  
  
---|---|---  
  
AB_PHOTO

JSESSIONID

WC_ACTIVEPOINTER_#

WC_AUTHENTICATION_#

WC_PERSISTENT

WC_SESSION_ESTABLISHED

WC_USERACTIVITY_#

cartId

cartItemId

cartValue

cartSize

WC_pickUpStore

userLanguage,

currentDeliveryCountry,

usergeo,

userCountry,

prefShipCtry

| 

Arcadia WCS (Internal)

| 

These cookies are used to support the website and user experience, without these the website would not work  
  
**5\. Third party cookies**

**5.1 What third party cookies do we use and why**

Some cookies may be set by third parties when you visit this website. Generally, these third party cookies do not collect personal data from which the third party would be able to identify individual customers.  
These third parties may be suppliers who partner with us to deliver our website, companies that participate with us in affiliate marketing programmes and other third parties who deliver products that enhance the user experience and consequently assist generating sales. Data from these cookies is collected directly by those third parties and not by us. These cookies are controlled by the third parties, who must ensure they comply with their legal obligations when using cookies and collecting your information, including by making their privacy policies available to you and allowing you to change your mind. Please check the third-party websites for more information about these cookies and how to manage them.

Third party partners that may set cookies on this website include:

**Business Partner**

| 

**Cookie Purpose**  
  
---|---  
  
ecustomeropinions.com

| 

In order to provide you with a better service, occasionally we'll ask if you'd like to complete a survey. This cookie's sole purpose is to remember if we've asked you to do so recently, and it contains no personal information.  
  
Affiliate Window, Linkshare, Zanox

| 

These cookies are only set if you get to the confirmation page after checkout. It is used to track whether we then owe any money as a commission to a site (affiliate) which has referred business to us.  
  
Double Click

| 

Double Click uses cookies to calculate payment for effective advertising based on clicks and conversions by tracking them. This is part of Google's conversion tag and more information on how the cookie operates and how you can manage these cookies is available at <http://www.google.com/intl/en_GB/policies/technologies/ads/>  
  
Sizmek

| 

Sizmek uses cookies to track what ads a user sees and engages with. These cookies are also used to track how a user that has seen or clicked on these ads engages with the different pages on the site so that they can accurately report on which pages the ads drove traffic to.  
  
Facebook

| 

Facebook use Cookies and similar technologies to show you ads on and off Facebook Services. Facebook work with advertising companies to help advertisers show people ads based on other websites or apps those people have visited, among other factors.  
  
Google

| 

To help Google partners manage their advertising and websites, Google offer many products, including AdSense, AdWords, Google Analytics, and a range of DoubleClick-branded services. When you visit a page that uses one of these products, either on one of Google’s sites or one of our partners’, various cookies can get used. Google may use cookies for a number of purposes, such as to stop you from seeing the same ad over and over again, to detect and stop click fraud, and to show ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as ads based on websites you have visited). Our analytics service provider’s privacy policy is available at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.  
  
Twitter

| 

To help Twitter deliver ads, measure their performance, and make them more relevant to you based on criteria like your activity on Twitter and visits to our ad partners' websites.  
  
Ad Networks 

| 

Different networks use cookies to segment and categorise different types of audience, dependant on behaviour (profiling). These audience segments are then used to predict what interests a category will have and what ads they will most like. Thy help deliver relevant ads to a user’s measured interests. We contract with different ad brokers from time to time and they each interact with a range of members that also change from time to time. They normally cannot identify you in a “real world” sense and do not provide us with the information they collect from their cookies.  
  
  **Flash cookies**

| 

We may display video content on our website using Adobe Flash Player.  Adobe uses Flash cookies to improve your experience as a user.  If you wish to disable or delete a Flash cookie, please visit Adobe Flashplayer Security Settings.  Please bear in mind that if you disable Flash cookies you will be unable to access certain content on our website which uses Adobe Flash Player, such as videos.  

**5.2 Social buttons**  
If you 'share' our content with friends through social networks – such as Facebook, Google and Twitter - you may be sent cookies from these third party websites. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.

**6\. How to manage cookies**  
You can enable or disable cookies by changing your website browser settings to accept or reject cookies as required. How to do this will depend on the browser you use. We have provided further information below on how to check which browser you use and how to manage cookies. Please bear in mind that if cookies are not enabled on your computer, your activities will be restricted to browsing this website and you will not be able to add products to your shopping bag and buy them.

**7\. Checking which browser you use**  
If you are using a PC - go to 'Help' and select the 'About' option.  
If you are using a Mac - click on the Apple menu within the browser and select the 'About' option.  
Once you know which brower you are using, follow the instructions below to check if you have cookies enabled on your computer

**8.Checking cookies**

**8.1 PCs**  
Microsoft Internet Explorer 6,7,8

  * Go to 'Tools' at the top of your browser window. Select 'Internet options'. Click on the 'Privacy' tab.
  * Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below to enable cookies

Mozilla Firefox 

  * Go to 'Tools' and select Options
  * Click the Privacy icon
  * Click on Cookies and choose 'allow sites to set cookies.

Google Chrome

  * Go to 'Tools' and select Options
  * Click 'Under the Hood' and select the 'Content settings' button within the 'Privacy' section
  * Choose 'Allow local data to be set'

8.2 Macs  
Safari on OSX

  * Click 'Safari' and select '
  * Click 'Security' then 'Accept cookies'

Mozilla and Netscape on OSX

  *  Click on 'Mozilla' or 'Netscape' and select 'Preferences'
  *  Find ‘Cookies’ under 'Privacy & Security'
  *  Select 'Enable cookies for the originating web site only'

Microsoft Internet Explorer on OSX

  * Click 'Explorer' and select 'Preferences'
  * Find 'Cookies' under ‘Receiving Files’
  * Select 'Never Ask'

Opera

  * Click 'Menu' and select 'Settings'
  * Select 'Preferences' and then '
  * Select 'Accept

If you are not happy with the way that we use cookies then you should delete Dorothy Perkin's cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called “Incognito” in Chrome, “InPrivate” for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.)

**9\. Other details you should know**  
Our Cookies Policy explains how we at Dorothy Perkins Limited collect data from your computer, mobile or other device when using our website. If you would like to get in touch, you can write to us at: Customer Care, Burton Business Park, Torre Road, Leeds, LS9 6DJ. We reserve the right to update this Cookies Policy at any time but won't send communications regarding minor changes, so we will only provide you with an updated Cookies Policy when we make changes to cookies that we need you to know about and agree to. The latest Cookies Policy with any other updates will always be available on our website for you to check.  
Even if you do not consent to or change your mind about our cookies, you may still see our advertising on line but this will be general advertising or page/context specific advertising and not shaped by your browsing or shopping behaviour as an individual.

**Making a request to our partners   **

We partner with other companies to ensure that you get additional services and helpful add-ons to improve your experience with us. In some instances you must contact these partners directly to submit a privacy request.  

We've compiled a list (below) of who these partners are and what exactly they do.  We've also given you a link to their privacy policy, which contains information about how to make a privacy request to them. Not all of these third parties process your personal data but if you think they have please do not hesitate to contact them directly.  

THIRD PARTY NAME 

| 

WHAT THEY DO  

| 

LINK TO PRIVACY POLICY   
  
---|---|---  
  
KLARNA 

| 

Klarna provide finance options to pay for online purchases at a later date 

| 

PAYPAL 

| 

Paypal is a third-party service that lets you pay without entering payment details to stores directly   

| 

UNIDAYS

| 

Unidays are a third party who verify student status and provide student discount codes based on this  

| 

STUDENT BEANS

| 

Student Beans are a third party who verify student status and provide student discount codes based on this 

| 

ABA 

| 

ABA Research provide feedback to companies based on customer opinions 

| 

INTELLIGENT REACH 

| 

Intelligent Research are an ecommerce software provider optimising product visibility  

| 

DRESSIPI 

| 

Dressipi provide a fashion-personalisation service 

| 

CONVERSANT 

| 

Conversant are a digital marketing provider 

| 

ZANOX 

| 

Also known as Awin. Please refer to Awin entry 

| 

AWIN 

| 

Awin are an affiliate marketing network that allows companies to advertise their products 

| 

CURALATE 

| 

Curulate is a platform that allows us to select and upload photos that people send to us to our websites, such as being featured in an ‘as seen on me’ segment 

| 

TWITTER 

| 

Twitter is a social media platform  

| 

NEW DAY 

| 

New Day are a credit and financial provider   

| 

RAKUTEN MARKETING  

| 

Rakuten Marketing are an affiliate marketing company, that deliver a personalised advertising experience 

| 

WORLDPAY 

| 

Worldpay provide payments processing technology  

| 

BAZAARVOICE

| 

BazaarVoice provide a product review service

|
